{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Ceiling Fan Installation Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40243/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40243,"taskName":"Ceiling Fan - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Ceiling Fan","xmTaskDescriptor":"Ceiling Fan Installation Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":37,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Ceiling addition attic conditioning air","textMessagingName":"Instl Ceiling Fan","rolloverLongDesc":"These are the large slow fans so often seen in tropical climates that stir the air in a room. They are often combined with lighting fixtures. Experts can properly mount the heavy fixtures \u0026 make the appropriate electrical connections.","rolloverShortDesc":"Handles both the mounting \u0026 electrical aspects.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Ceiling Fan.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Ceiling Fan Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace Ceiling Fans","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":25,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Ceiling Fan Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Ceiling Fan - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Ceiling Fan Installation Project","urlName":"Ceiling-Fan-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Ceiling Fan Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Ceiling,addition,attic,conditioning,air,outdoor,Fan","emcCategoryOid":-12029,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":550,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40243/":{"taskOID":40243,"originalTaskOID":40243,"setID":550,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":3052,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Fan Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of ceiling fan installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4088,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4086,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500702,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the fan(s) for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the fan(s) for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3054,"questionDisplayText":"Fan Control","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the ceiling fan be controlled? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pull string","answerDisplayText":"Pull string","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3055,"questionDisplayText":"Fan Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What quality level of ceiling fan do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2140,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Economy grade","answerDisplayText":"Economy grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium grade","answerDisplayText":"Medium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Premium grade","answerDisplayText":"Premium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":3052,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Fan Installation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of ceiling fan installation is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4088,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4086,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4088,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to remove an existing lighting fixture and install a ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4086,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","answerDisplayText":"Need to install a ceiling fan in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4091,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","answerDisplayText":"Need to replace existing ceiling fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500702,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the fan(s) for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the fan(s) for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3054,"questionDisplayText":"Fan Control","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How will the ceiling fan be controlled? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pull string","answerDisplayText":"Pull string","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pull string","answerDisplayText":"Pull string","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":3055,"questionDisplayText":"Fan Quality","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What quality level of ceiling fan do you want installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2140,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Economy grade","answerDisplayText":"Economy grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium grade","answerDisplayText":"Medium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Premium grade","answerDisplayText":"Premium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2140,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Economy grade","answerDisplayText":"Economy grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3797,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium grade","answerDisplayText":"Medium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Premium grade","answerDisplayText":"Premium grade","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}